{"id":"2017_10","name":"Romans2017_10","memoryVerse":"“Consequently, just as one trespass resulted in condemnation for all people, so also one righteous act resulted in  justification and life for all people.” – Romans 5:18","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_10_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 6:1-4.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"6:1-4"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_10_3","questionText":"3. What thoughts in chapter 5 prompted Paul to ask the question in 6:1, and why? ","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_4","questionText":"4. What happens when Christians believe their sin does not matter? ","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_5","questionText":"5. When have you been tempted to sin because you knew God would forgive you? How might these verses strengthen you to fight sin instead?  ","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 6:1-4.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"6:1-4"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_10_6","questionText":"6. Who are “we” and “us” in these verses?  If you are part of this group, rewrite verse 2 as your own statement. ","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_7","questionText":"7. Describe the spiritual reality to which water baptism points. (See also Acts 1:5; 2:38; 1 Corinthians 12:13;  Galatians 3:26-27; Colossians 2:11-12.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Acts","verse":"1:5"},{"book":"Acts","verse":"2:38"},{"book":"1 Corinthians","verse":"12:13"},{"book":"Galatians","verse":"3:26-27"},{"book":"Colossians","verse":"2:11-12"}]},{"id":"2017_10_8","questionText":"8.  Specifically how does Paul say believers have died to sin?  If Christ is your Savior, how have you experienced this death personally and how are you now living a new life? (See also Romans 5:12-21; 2 Corinthians 5:14-21.) ","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"5:12-21"},{"book":"2 Corinthians","verse":"5:14-21"}]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 6:5-10.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"6:5-10"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_10_9","questionText":"9. From these verses, name ways believers are united with Christ.","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_10","questionText":"10. What does Paul mean by “the old self ”? (See also Ephesians 4:22-24; Colossians 3:9-10.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Ephesians","verse":"4:22-24"},{"book":"Colossians","verse":"3:9-10"}]},{"id":"2017_10_11","questionText":"11. For which aspects of your union with Christ will you thank God, and where do you need His help to believe He has set you free from sin? (See also Colossians 2:11-15.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Colossians","verse":"2:11-15"}]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 6:9-11.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"6:9-11"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_10_12","questionText":"12. List facts about Jesus from verses 9-10. How does verse 11 connect your life with what is true of Jesus?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_13","questionText":"13. What does it look like to be dead to sin but alive to Christ: In your home? In your school, workplace or community? In your church?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Romans 6:1-11.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"6:1-11"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_10_14","questionText":"14. What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_10_15","questionText":"15. Homiletics for group and administrative leaders: Romans 6:1-11","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"6:1-11"}]}]}}}